<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Procedures on Syniti Documentation</title>
    <link>https://heathercloward.github.io/data-services-autogen/use_cases/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Procedures on Syniti Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://heathercloward.github.io/data-services-autogen/use_cases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Build and Refresh Data Services Jobs</title>
      <link>https://heathercloward.github.io/data-services-autogen/use_cases/build_and_refresh_ds_jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathercloward.github.io/data-services-autogen/use_cases/build_and_refresh_ds_jobs/</guid>
      <description>Build and Refresh Data Services Jobs Before Data Services jobs can be created, the Data Service Repository and datastores must be configured. Refer to Configure a Data Services Repository and Configure a Data Services Datastore for more information.
An AutoGen request contains all of the metadata required to generate the Data Services Jobs for the specific target. The AutoGen request takes the form of a number of metadata definition files that are compressed and sent to dspCloud™ for processing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure Proxy Sever Settings</title>
      <link>https://heathercloward.github.io/data-services-autogen/use_cases/configure_proxy_server_settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathercloward.github.io/data-services-autogen/use_cases/configure_proxy_server_settings/</guid>
      <description>Configure Proxy Sever Settings To use Data Services AutoGen, the web server must be able to establish outbound connections to sites hosted by BackOffice Associates®. This may require firewall exceptions and/or proxy server configuration on the Parameters page.
To configure proxy server settings for AutoGen:
 Click the Automation tab in the Quick Panel.
 Select the Object for which the proxy server settings are being set up.
 Click the Build and Refresh Data Services icon in the Page toolbar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure a Data Services Datastore</title>
      <link>https://heathercloward.github.io/data-services-autogen/use_cases/configure_a_ds_datastore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathercloward.github.io/data-services-autogen/use_cases/configure_a_ds_datastore/</guid>
      <description>Configure a Data Services Datastore On the Data Services Datastores Mappings page, configure the Data Services datastores to support auto-generation.
A Data Services Repository can be registered at the Process Area: Object level or at the Process Area level (for example, the same Data Service Repository can be assigned to different Process Area: Objects). The level at which the repository is registered influences how Data Services Projects are organized. In either case, Console is a required data source, so a pair of datastores must be registered: one for Console and one for the related dsw* database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure a Data Services Repository</title>
      <link>https://heathercloward.github.io/data-services-autogen/use_cases/configure_a_ds_repository/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathercloward.github.io/data-services-autogen/use_cases/configure_a_ds_repository/</guid>
      <description>Configure a Data Services Repository On the Data Services Repositories page, set up the Data Services Repository to accept the Data Services Jobs.
When configuring a Data Services Repository, configure the Web Services connection, then configure the connection to the repository database.
To configure a Data Services Repository in AutoGen:
 Click the Automation tab in the Quick Panel.
 Select the Object for which the Data Services Repository is being set up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Import Data Services Objects</title>
      <link>https://heathercloward.github.io/data-services-autogen/use_cases/import_ds_objects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathercloward.github.io/data-services-autogen/use_cases/import_ds_objects/</guid>
      <description>Import Data Services Objects Use this page to [Build and Refresh Data Services Jobs.](Build_and_Refresh_DS_Jobs.htm)  To access this page:
 Click the Automation tab in the Quick Panel. Select the Object for which the request is being generated. Click the Build and Refresh Data Services icon in the Page toolbar; the *AutoGen Data Services* page displays. Click the Import Objects icon; the *Autogen BODS Requests* page displays.           Field Description   COMMENT Displays a comment regarding the Data Services Jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup and Configuration for Data Services AutoGen</title>
      <link>https://heathercloward.github.io/data-services-autogen/use_cases/setup_and_configuration_for_data_services_autogen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathercloward.github.io/data-services-autogen/use_cases/setup_and_configuration_for_data_services_autogen/</guid>
      <description> Setup and Configuration for Data Services AutoGen Data Services AutoGen provides the ability to generate Data Services Jobs that perform target enrichments and validations and post load validations.
Before using Data Services AutoGen:
 Create the Contexts for Migration Projects Register the Data Services Repository as a Data Source in Common Configure Data Services Functionality Add a Target in Target Design Add Rules in Target Design Sync Map and Target Design  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>