<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Configuration on Syniti Documentation</title>
    <link>https://heathercloward.github.io/Design/Config/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Configuration on Syniti Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://heathercloward.github.io/Design/Config/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Access Target Design</title>
      <link>https://heathercloward.github.io/Design/Config/Access_Design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathercloward.github.io/Design/Config/Access_Design/</guid>
      <description>Access Target Design Before using Target Design, a Wave, a Process Area (the combination of which is called a context), and an Object used in the data migration project must have been created in Console.
Refer to Create the Contexts for Migration Projects for more information.
Target Design is accessible through dspMigrate™ by clicking the Context bar. It is not accessible through the Navigation pane.
Refer to Context, the Context Bar, and Navigation for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add Custom Criticality Levels</title>
      <link>https://heathercloward.github.io/Design/Config/Add_Custom_Criticality_Levels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathercloward.github.io/Design/Config/Add_Custom_Criticality_Levels/</guid>
      <description>Add Custom Criticality Levels Criticality can be set for a Target field and is used for reporting purposes.
Three criticality levels are installed by default: High, Medium and Low. These DSP-supplied values cannot be edited or deleted.
New levels can be added. Once saved, these levels are available for selection in the CRITICALITY list box on the Target Fields page.
To add a criticality level in Target Design:
 Select Configuration &amp;gt; Criticality in the Navigation pane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add Custom Requirement Settings</title>
      <link>https://heathercloward.github.io/Design/Config/Add_Custom_Requirement_Settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathercloward.github.io/Design/Config/Add_Custom_Requirement_Settings/</guid>
      <description>Add Custom Requirement Settings Requirement settings can be set for a Target field and are used for reporting purposes.
Four requirement levels are installed by default. These DSP-supplied values cannot be edited or deleted.
The values are:
 Business Required – Required to meet a business rule or otherwise meet a business need Technical Required – Required by the system Conditional – Required depending on certain conditions Optional – Not required  New Requirement settings can be added.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>